Students, we have been blessed with cerulean skies. Couldn't have asked for better weather this fine sports day.
Remember, demonstrate good sportsmanship, and just have fun out there.
Very stirring words. Thank you for that, sir.
And now, the pledge of fair play.
The pledge.
We, the proud student body of Katakiri High School.
Is it me, or is the press looking a little blue?
Yeah, despite his red hair.
That contrast is crazy.
Looks like both of his arms are still intact.
Hey, good thing it's cool outside, huh?
Lots of people are in long sleeves.
Oh, you're right.
Sengoku had a fit when he heard you were fired up for this.
Called you a traitor.
Truth be told, I think this kind of stuff is boring.
I never had a reason to try before.
But, this year I'll actually have to put in effort.
To beat you.
Now, without further ado, let the Katakiri High School sports day begin!
Now, without further ado, let's see.
意味をくれたこと
きっと知らないだろう
君が呼ぶ僕の名前
由来より大きな
意味をくれたこと
飲み干した甘いサイダー
見せかえる僕を笑った
作った笑顔なんかもいらないね
どうしてどうして
もらってばかりいる僕を
愛しいというの
僕は何を返して返して
生きて生きるんだろうか
淡しい想いが満ちていく
この感情の名前をそっと
君に伝うよ
それを渡して
Right off the bat, the East and West are neck and neck.
No doubt the second-year girls' hurdle had everyone sweating.
Any thoughts, Mr. Nakamine?
It was insane.
Yeah, it was! Second-year ladies came to represent!
So, the third-year teams are running the hurdle race next, right?
Yep, yep.
It's go time!
Have fun, but safety first.
Yay!
Since you have legs, and I'm partnerless for the three-legged race,
what do you say we team up, huh?
Sign up for Top of the Pole while you're at it.
The East is short one guy.
I would rather be a shellfish right now.
Next up is a third-year girls' hurdle race.
Well, I gotta run.
Go and kick all the bats!
I didn't realize you were racing, too.
I bet that you're super-duper quick, aren't you?
Nah, I'd say I'm average at best.
Yeah, right, like I believe that.
I shall mow down any who stand in my way!
You've got this!
You do!
The best is the best!
Hear that?
Miyamoto's cheering his heart out for Remy to win!
I believe that he's cheering for the entirety of the West team.
Next team, line up!
Since he's watching, I'm gonna work extra hard.
Yeah, um, he wasn't cheering just for you.
If Remy wins, Miyamoto belongs to her.
K, Kion, Kion!
Uh, Kion?
What?
Get set!
Hey!
Ayasaki's fast!
He's a dark horse?
He wants!
Ayasaki is leading!
He fights!
Oof, that sounded painful.
I think she kicked it on purpose.
Metal.
She said that stuff to get under my skin!
Damn it!
Look, Mugs!
Team East is trailing behind!
Thanks, Captain Obvious!
The East girl bringing up the rear is looking really intense.
Yeah, you kinda sorta know it.
East takes first, and West takes second!
I tell my boyfriend not to slack, then come in dead last.
Man, what is my deal?
Huh?
Honey!
Don't give up!
Huh?
She's the enemy!
No cheering!
Finish strong, even if it's last place, okay?
Take the bed out of hell!
He's kind of burst of speed from nowhere!
Kion Kion!
Could you not with the Kion Kion stuff?
Because you and Miyamoto are so lovey-dovey with each other,
Rami can hardly bear the thought of stealing him away!
Freakin' puppet master!
Just kidding!
Rami's heart belongs to Sengoku!
You just get blustered so easily, but it's really adorable!
Now listen, you!
Hey!
There you are!
Got a sec?
Did I interrupt you?
We're through!
So I'll be going now!
I'll even take your sign!
Oh!
Nice!
Is your leg okay?
That hurdle race was impressive!
It was last place!
You looked like a regular pro during your practice sessions,
but then you stalled out for the real thing!
Why?
Because of you!
That's why!
Wait!
Then why'd you speed up at the end?
That was also your fault!
I'm confused!
And I'm gonna watch the next race!
You should make your way back too!
Okay!
Before you go...
Thanks...
For cheering...
Made me happy!
Sure!
Miyamura!
Check it out!
Look who's also repping Team West!
Can she even lift the tug-of-war rope?
Huh?
Oh!
Pori-senpai!
Watch me compete, okay?
She is on the other team, right?
I think so!
Go, Sawada!
Look who's also repping Team West.
Can't she even lift the tug-of-war rope?
Party Senpai!
Watch me compete, okay?
She is on the other team, right?
I think so.
Go, Sawada!
Give it all you got, girl!
Or not.
For a quick second, I thought our cheering was too loud.
Dude, who doesn't love having people in their corner?
You eat that stuff up too, don't you?
I've never really done the cheer thing on Sports Day.
And nobody ever cheered for me.
I suggest that you start by cheering more for your team than your opponents, rookie.
I got caught up in the moment.
Sorry.
Be real nice if you could drown out the other team while I compete in the upcoming obstacle course.
If there's one person who won't snub you for cheering loud, it's your boy.
Right.
I tried so hard, but the West team lost.
Hey, don't let it get you down.
There were a whole bunch of jocks on Team East's side.
I wanted you to see me emerge victorious and look cool!
Take your cheers off Team East, sirf.
Ishikawa is next stop.
Cheer really loud!
I wish I were on the West side.
My team sounds like they'll kill me.
Where's the prez?
Said he was only participating in the mandatory stuff.
Now on your marks...
Get set!
And the fellas are off to brave the obstacle course.
First up is the balance beam, and neither team is ready to give up the lead just yet.
Ishikawa, keep going!
Go away!
Go away, Ishikawa!
Run!
All together.
Go for gold!
Ishikawa!
Go for gold! Ishikawa!
One more.
Ready? Stay strong!
Nearly there!
Oh, calling your name.
Lucky you.
Yeah, except there's also one high-pitched guy mixed in.
How about that?
Finally found your voice.
Gosh, which team would pull off the win?
Ishikawas!
So you two tied?
That's pretty darn good for somebody like Iura, right?
Yoshikawa's words, not mine.
Though you have my praise as well.
That's praise? Speaking of, where are the girls at?
They're getting ready.
It's almost time for the cheer competition.
All right, guys!
The moment of pom-poms is upon us!
First up, the East Team third years!
Say it loud, everyone! Go!
East!
A-S-T-B-I-K-U!
Wee!
Oh, isn't somebody the greatest?
Oh, absolutely!
I've never seen a cheer like this before.
That officially makes two of us.
I wonder how Kyochan's boyfriend feels watching this unique display.
Oh, we lost him.
Figures.
Take courage, Team West!
Ready?
Okay!
Here we go!
We're the West!
Win, win, West!
No stress, we're best.
Put our powers to the best!
So Team East was a hit with the girls, and Team West won over the guys.
Wasn't that going to be a little too cute?
Deep breaths, Fres. Deep breaths.
Right, right, bounce and up.
Now punch to the left and pose.
Fight hard!
Drink big!
I did it.
That was so much fun.
It was so much fun.
That was seriously hot stuff.
Like, I'm talking sweltering.
Right back at ya.
You're a star, honey!
Oh, shucks.
Yoshikawa!
You rocked it out there, Kono!
Your entire team looked fantastic!
You really mean it?
Thank you.
You could've let me struggle all on my own.
But you took the time to help me learn the routines.
I should've thanked you sooner, I know.
You missed sincerity over here!
I did mean every word.
Now there's a chance.
Ishikawa noticed me in a good way.
Dude, you knew it was coming, so what is your deal?
I wanted to see her with pom-poms and a skirt.
Hey, Miyamura, do you have a second?
You need me?
Yes, one of our boys is out with a nasty cold.
Will you fill in?
Pretty please.
Last I checked, you weren't signed up for any solo events.
That's true.
But still, are you sure I'm your guy?
I wouldn't have asked if you weren't the one I wanted.
Yeah, of course.
I'll be right there.
Thanks.
You'll do awesome.
Miyamura came in third.
What a loser.
These events should just be for athletic people.
That's it.
Made me happy.
You'll do awesome.
Dude who doesn't love having people in their corner.
I guess, with the right people, sports day is actually kind of...
Now, the time's come for our scavenger hunt.
The only co-ed event we'll have today.
Find whatever's written inside your envelope and...
Hey, if you have glasses, get over here!
Yo, ponytail!
First one across the finish line will be me.
That's great.
I can help you reach some other goals in life too, you know.
Hey, for curiosity's sake, what's on that slip of paper there?
The youngest teacher at school?
That's a point for each!
Yuki took the top spot.
Better hustle myself.
I'm gonna finish first too.
Oh, I'm sorry!
This one's all yours, okay?
No, you take it.
Rory?
Miyamura?
What are you doing here?
Well, I'm subbing for someone who's out sick with a cold.
Come on!
Go, Hori!
No, I'm falling behind!
He's just doing a whole bunch of nothing out there.
Both Miyamura and Hori seem caught off guard.
Sometime today!
Stay focused, Kyochan.
You do realize what side you're on, right?
The sidelines, preferably.
They were searching for a student to even out the count for this very event.
But I slipped away!
Why are you proud of this?
Wait!
Stop pulling!
No!
Could members from both East and West have drawn the same thing?
That is illegal!
Like, no!
He is what I need to find!
The same goes for me!
Please don't pop my shoulders!
It's...
Just hang tight!
Do your best, Sengoku!
Are you cheering?
I'm not competing!
This isn't fair!
Ha ha ha!
All right!
The last two players have crossed the finish line!
Simultaneously!
And they both brought the student council president!
Okay, will you two explain already?
Was I really the only person who fit the description of what you needed to find?
Hmm?
Kyo-chan's I get.
But what's your excuse?
There are other skinny boys!
I...
Figured I should find the skinniest one.
Sweet!
I can't believe you!
The third-year boys' cavalry battle is starting soon!
All competitors, assemble and get ready!
You'll obviously be our rider!
He'll obviously be our rider!
Yet again!
My weight betrays me!
If either of you were a base, you'd snap in half.
We're human beings, not bridges.
Come on, Sengoku!
Since we're in it, let's win it!
Yeah, okay.
Hip, hip!
Dude!
You're supposed to say hooray!
Yeah, the first victim of the Sengoku.
Hooray!
Understood.
Yeah, yeah!
Oh!
Yanagi's a rider, too?
Yes.
Thanks.
All the riders are the least competitive people here.
And up we go!
Whoa!
Oh!
Maybe getting into this a little now.
Are ya?
About time.
The view from the top is a beautiful sight to see!
Sounds like we got a real general on our hands.
Literally.
Amazing what a change of scenery can do.
Let's do it to it, guys!
Right.
Sengoku!
Score at least one point or die trying!
Right now, Mercy!
Oh, wow.
Woody's cheering for the Prez.
That's what teammates do, so of course she is.
Yeah, but aren't you kind of ticked off?
So, like, what's the game plan?
Well, since the Prez is so clever and all.
Listen, I have an idea.
So, who do we cheer for?
The riders snatching all the headbands or everyone involved?
Both, because they're all working hard.
But a lot's writing on the riders, so maybe save most of your cheers for them.
Okay.
This game's pretty complex.
Miyamura!
We're rooting for you!
Goodbye!
You can do it!
Is Miyamura the only one they care about?
Sengoku!
Doesn't listening to your girlfriend cheer on Miyamura get you fired up?
Teammates are supposed to encourage each other.
What exactly are you trying to imply?
Ignore me.
It's time!
Take your places, everyone!
Keep it clean and to the best team go the glory!
Ready?
Let's play the best!
Wait!
I feel like I was pretty close!
This Team West guy's just grabbing at random!
Holy crap!
Hey, keep your eyes open there, buddy!
It won't help.
I forgot my glasses.
Nanagi's doing way better than I thought he would.
Mr. President.
This point is mine!
So give it here!
It seems Team West is as nimble as a feather in the summer breeze.
Anybody could have dodged those wimpy swipes.
They can sabotage the offensive, yeah?
You got it.
Where does Doggy Dog's spirit come from?
I think he tapped into his inner general.
Okay.
Concentrate!
They're still in the game, Sengoku!
Kill it, Harise!
Behead him if you have to!
You want Miyamura to die?
God, his evasion technique's down to an art.
Miyamura, I'm about at my limit here.
Can you get it in one go?
You're tired?
Makes sense.
Playing as a horse is no joke.
Something on your mind?
My nose is at you like crazy.
What a coincidence.
Mine too.
It's gonna come down to who wears out first.
Unless...
What's with the face?
So, Prez.
Just wondering.
But have you noticed that strange girl on your shoulder?
Right there.
Oh!
Waaaa!
Um...
Looks like Team West takes the win for the cavalry battle!
So they were at a standstill,
and Singako turned his head for no reason.
Yup.
Awesome job, Yamura!
Man, well, guess it's whatever.
It is not whatever! Have you seen the score?
Come on, Remy. Gotta move these chairs.
Until the afternoon, we were the ones ahead.
But isn't it nice that Sengoku could be on the winning team?
You practiced the chair enough to win the whole sports day for us.
Not entirely accurate.
You did it enough to be the cutest one out there.
Like, it wasn't even a contest.
If you say so.
No wonder my nose hurt. It's already red from sunburn.
Sheen just gonna make so much fun of me.
Hey, Hori. That you?
Oh, you're still here?
Yeah, but more importantly, where are you off to?
Oh, and why are you wearing that?
Sports day's over now.
Yeah, I know, but the girls are taking a group shot before we leave for the day.
I wore the boys' uniform for the actual event, so I thought I'd change for the pick.
I did hand-make these pom-poms.
Well, the boys' uniform looked great on you.
Did it?
I have a hunch I'm the reason we won the cheer battle.
At least my sunburn hides my blush.
I had a cheerleader long before sports day even started.
She's been in my corner rooting for me to succeed.
And she's shining brighter than ever.
Am I cute?
I was, uh, copying Ayasaki.
You are cute.
Cute beyond belief.
You big dummy!
Dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy!
As far as I'm concerned, today wasn't just my last sports day.
It was my first.
And it was a lot of fun.
The day may have ended, but that feeling stayed with me.
All that I yonder
You were the same thing before
You're the same thing again
Don't forget that you're the same thing
I don't want to leave the days too late
You don't want to leave the days
What are you doing?
That day is too late
Don't forget that it's perfect
To go right ahead and stop
In this beautiful place
I truly believe you are
You look good
It's a decentralize
People like me
Alice
Are you there?
I don't know
You're we gracias
I'm so sad, don't go on,でも
君に飛べるように
出会えるように
できてたなら